Dunder Mifflin.
This is Rolando.
Oh, yes.
She's been expecting your call.
(knocks)
[Karen] Yeah.
- Karen?
He's on line one.
Thanks, Ro.
Hey. We finally connected.
How's Scranton?
I am the regional manager
of Dunder Mifflin Utica branch.
Turns out it's a pretty easy gig
when your boss isn't an idiot
and your boyfriend's not
in love with somebody else.
Look, all I'm saying is it would
be a great opportunity and we'd
love to have you come aboard.
So think about it. Okay?
Okay, bye.
Look, for the record,
a certain Scranton
salesman approached me. Okay?
- This is perfect!
- He looks like your twin.
This is a dummy.
Ala, Ferris Bueller's Day Off.
We've tied a string to the
wrist, which goes to the door.
When somebody opens the door,
the hand goes down,
hits the remote,
turns on the tape recorder,
which is me snoring.
Now nobody knows whether I am
here or whether I am gone.
I'll know.
But you will not tell anyone.
- I won't need to because we'll
be together, playing hooky.
- Sometimes, most of the time I
will be with Ryan or Darryl.
(knock on door)
Yes. Oh good, good.
Stanley first victim.
This is what I want you to do.
Go out.
Come back in.
We're going to hide.
I want you to tell me
if this looks like me. Okay?
- I don't understand
why sleeping
at your desk is better
than you not being here.
Just go out and come back in.
(snoring sound)
- I got an offer from Utica
for more money.
And I'm going to take it.
- What?
(door shuts)
(upbeat theme music)
- Hey, everyone. Can I have your
attention, please?
I just thought you all should
know that Stanley Hudson is
planning on leaving us
because our old friend Karen
from Utica is going to give
him more money to work there.
- Okay!
(clapping)
[Michael] No, no, no no!
No, you completely
misinterpreted my tone.
This is a horrible thing.
Clearly, Karen is trying to get
back at us because
Jim dumped her.
- Oh, I don't think
that's what's happening.
Okay, well, smarty pants.
Then why is she trying
to take Stanley from us?
- I think it's because
of my sales record.
That could not possibly be it.
You cannot take the hilarious
black guy from the office.
Stanley is part of what makes
this branch so extraordinary.
The bluesy wisdom,
the sassy remarks,
the crossword puzzles,
the smile, those big,
watery red eyes.
I don't know how George Bush
did it when Colin Powell left.
And if Utica thinks that they
are going to poach Stanley,
they have another thing coming.
Are you gleeful over this?
Is working out for you, Jim?
- It's completely
unrelated, so...
Was it worth it?
Was she worth it?
Yep, she was.
- Look at Pam, everybody.
She likes this.
Oh. No, you missed it.
Now she's ordinary again.
- How can I get you to stay?
- Money.
Yeah. We all want money.
But there is none in the budget.
So tell me why you're
really leaving.
Money.
- More money, more problems,
Stanley.
You of all people
should know that.
Let me ask you this.
- If I were...
- Money.
Oscar, did you bring it?
To be Edwardian.
His best work.
- Okay, well, I have
the tablecloth.
- Don't forget the flatware.
- Sure thing, Pam.
- Can't wait.
- [Angela] Sure thing, Pam.
- Fru fru club.
- [Kevin] Must be nice.
Look at me.
I wear underwear.
Oscar, Toby and I are founding
members of the
Finer Things Club.
We meet once a month to discuss
books and art, celebrate culture
in a very civilized way.
Sometimes the debate can get
heated, but we're
always respectful.
There is no paper, no plastic
and no work talk allowed.
It's very exclusive.
- Besides having sex with men,
I would say
The Finer Things Club is
the gayest thing about me.
I love the Finer Things Club.
My ex wife used to have a book
club and I would read their book
and sometimes listen
from the kitchen.
The Finer Things Club was not
sanctioned by the party
planning committee.
Renegade clubs are dangerous.
I squashed the Weight
Loss Buddy Support Group.
They didn't need to gather.
It was just gross.
- I don't know why I'm not
in the Finer Things Club.
It's bull crap.
(classical music plays)
- So, tell me again why I can't
be a part of your club.
- Because some people think
that you monopolize
the conversation
by trying to be funny.
- Oscar?
- Some people.
[Karen on phone] Hello?
- Fillippellers.
How they hanging?
- Michael...
- To the left? To the right?
- Listen, I'm...
- Okay, enough small talk.
- Go ahead.
- You called me.
Yes. Listen, umm...
You cannot tear Stanley
from his family like this.
- I'm pretty sure his family
is coming with him.
No, his work family.
Look, this is very hard for me,
but I'm going to give
you my best man.
You may have Toby.
Toby's not a salesperson.
You can train him.
He's very very smart and
funny and charming.
Aahhh!
You know, I can't do it.
Toby is the worst.
That was a bluff.
Listen, if you were going
to poach one of my guys, I am
going to poach one of yours.
Oooohhh...
- Goodbye, Michael.
- Okay. Goodbye.
Wait wait! Karen.
Could you transfer me to one
of your sales people, please?
Your best one.
(Karen hangs up)
- So, Stanley, are you
really out of here?
- Yep.
Looks that way.
I'm gonna miss you, man.
You've been like an uncle to me.
Like a kind old
Uncle Remus.
I want to stay in touch.
The Bernard Network or Bern-
network is constantly growing.
Always stay in touch with
everyone I've ever worked with.
Case in point, Stanley.
Just got his number.
1-800-Stanley.
How cool is it that he
got that number?
- If I was going
to socialize with Andy,
it would have happened by now.
- It's inappropriate
for Karen to poach Stanley.
Boiling makes
human flesh rubbery.
- I'm finally going
to get the good desk.
I have Ben Nugent on the line.
He is the top salesman in Utica.
- Hi, Ben. Michael Scott.
- Hi, Michael.
- I'm going to cut right
to the chase here.
Do you like magic?
Because I am a Genie in a bottle
and I'm going to grant you three
wishes.
To move to Scranton,
to have a great job
and to be my best friend.
- Aren't you the guy that hit
the woman with your car?
- (Pam chuckles)
- Get out.
Uhh...
Yeah, I also saved her life.
But I guess that's
not as grabby.
- Everyone says Scranton branch
is worse than Camden.
Didn't everyone from Stanford
quit, like immediately?
- No, I fired them.
And you're next.
So what do you say?
Seriously?
- What is that guy
talking about?
Scranton is not lame.
Here's the breakdown.
Utica is lame.
Utica is snoozeville.
Albany are the prepsters.
Umm...Camden is in a basement.
Nashua has no parking.
Akron is haunted.
Yonkers has the two hot girls.
And Scranton is the cool,
fun branch.
We're like Animal House.
- [Dwight] Found him.
(classical music plays)
Jim, we're getting crapped on.
Word is our branch sucks.
We have to do
something about it.
- So what are you going to do?
- What are we going to do?
We are going to make
a monster sale,
is what we're going to do.
- Corcoran dropped Staples.
- Did they?
- Yes, they did.
Oh, yes, they did.
And we are going to murder it.
You, me, Dwight are going
to jump in my PT Cruiser
we are going to crush this sale.
We are going to prove
what the hell is that music?
It's Vivaldi for Finer Things.
- That's the problem.
That's the problem.
We need rock and roll, Pam.
Rock and roll.
All right?
Oh, my God.
(classical music plays)
That's why people are leaving.
I...
I have no words.
**
Woo!
- Shotgun!
- Oh, you're driving, right?
- Yes, I am.
But I want shotgun for you.
- [Dwight] I wanted to
sit next to you.
- No, Dwight, Dwight, Jim is
sitting next to me.
You're going to sit in the back
left where I don't have
to see your ugly moon gob.
- Okay, that is so mean.
You know what?
- I'm not going.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dwight.
You're handsome.
You're a very handsome man.
Get in the car.
(car door slams)
Woo hoo!
(car engine revs)
- We just passed the
exit for Corcoran.
What? What? We did?
[Dwight and Michael]
Surprise! Yaah!
Hahaha!
- Yes! Look at his face!
Look at his face.
- What are we doing?
- Egg dripping, blaah.
Dwight, what are we doing?
Well, Gee, Jim, I don't know.
I guess there's no
sales call today.
- We are going on a panty
raid to Utica.
Is what we're doing.
- We're going to Utica?
- Uh huh!
(Dwight laughs)
I'm not going to Utica.
Yes, you are.
Oh, buckle up, Jim.
- No...
- We are going to make Karen
wish that she had
never been dumped by you.
(Michael and Dwight chanting)
Utica! Utica! Utica!
- Yow!
- I can't believe you guys.
I'm not going to go further
and piss off my ex-girlfriend.
- Are you calling Karen?
- No, I'm not calling Karen.
- He's lying.
- Yeah, get it.
- What are you doing?
Stop it! Dwight!
Gah! Hah!
Are you kidding me?
No communication
with the outside world, Jim.
(Dwight laughs)
Had to be done.
- Well, that kind of
sucks because
it had all the photos of my
brother's new baby on it.
That is too bad.
Shoot.
- Okay.
- Hey, Dwight, he found it.
You know what? I'm just going
to call a cab from here.
All right.
- You'll miss the best prank ever.
- All right.
Wait.
What are you planning on doing?
Do you really want to know?
- Oh, God.
- Follow me. Come here.
Here's what we brought.
We brought uniforms
from the warehouse.
I brought silly string.
Dwight brought gasoline
and chunks of rubber
to make stink bombs.
- Or real bombs.
- No, no. Not real bombs.
- Come on.
It'll be so bad ass.
- Maybe. I don't know.
It could be bad ass.
- Well..
- No. Absolutely
we're not doing this.
- Come on, I already filled
the bottles with the gas.
- It's going to be so bad ass!
- Are you kidding me?
We've been driving around
with this in the trunk
the whole time?
- Teach her to offer
Stanley more money.
- Can you imagine a
life where all
you have to do is summer
in the Italian countryside?
I know, right?
I just want to go and look
at art and swim in the Adriatic.
- And spend time
with George Emerson.
- That's what I would do.
- Absolutely.
He is great.
Totally!
I mean, come on.
Such a free spirit.
What are you doing?
- Just came to discuss
my favorite E.M. Forster novel.
(Andy sighs)
Pam...
These finger sandwiches look
finger licking delicious.
- I'm sorry, Andy,
but this is a closed club.
The Finer Things Club is
the most exclusive
club in this office.
Naturally, it's
where I need to be.
The party planning committee is
my backup, and Kevin's
band is my safety.
Fine.
I'll just
sit here in the common area
and read my book,
which just happens to be the
very same book you're reading.
All right.
Just know you're not
in The Finer Things Club.
Why can't I be in a club?
So there was no sales call?
[Jim] No.
Turns out it was just a really
bad idea involving fire,
but I think I fixed it.
- Wait, you're going
along with this now?
I have to.
Pam, if I'm not there,
someone's going to go
to jail or die.
- Right. And you wouldn't be
able to talk to Karen.
- Well, I promise you, that
has nothing to do with it.
A little bit.
- Well, yeah, I don't want to
see her get physically harmed.
That's for sure.
- Because you love her?
Because you love her very much?
- All right.
I'm going to go now.
- Okay.
Have fun with your girlfriend!
Okay, I will.
I'm kidding around.
We joke about that
stuff all the time.
I'm not really the jealous type,
so I don't care if
Jim sees Karen.
I care a little.
So the deal was
Dwight doesn't blow anything up,
and I wear costume.
And a mustache.
- So why did you
and Karen break up?
- Was it the sex?
- What?
- I can't imagine the sex being
bad. I mean her body...
- You know what?
Why don't we play that Alphabet
game that you were
talking about?
Okay, I will start.
Umm... "A".
* Hey, my name is Alan,
and my wife's name is Alice *
* We live in Alaska,
and we sell... *
Damn! What do we sell?
Umm...
Doesn't matter.
- I'm trying to think
of what we could sell.
It doesn't matter.
(liquid splashing)
What is that?
That sound. The air conditioning
leaking or something?
- That doesn't make sense.
It couldn't be.
What is that?
(liquid splashing)
Dwight, are you peeing?
I'm peeing in this empty can.
- Oh, my God!
- Man, that is disgusting!
- You said we couldn't
make any more stops.
I really had to go.
- (car skids)
- Michael, watch the road!
Hey! You're making me spray!
- I'll kill you, man!
- Oh my God!
- Michael, Michael!
Pull over!
Disgusting!
- I think I cut
my penis on the lid.
- [Pam] I think it's interesting
how Forster uses
Italy to represent
sexuality and passion.
(coins clanking)
And that also brought up themes
of fate and coincidence.
And Lucy is torn between
these two things.
She's torn between
passion and convention.
[Kevin] Damn it.
(banging)
(loud banging)
(indistinct)
[Kevin] Yes!
Dammit.
(microwave beeps)
- Made him sort of ahead
of his time as a writer.
Very brave choice, I thought.
- And George, his youthfulness,
his freedom, evokes
(beeping)
feelings.
Umm...
(beep beep beep)
(shouting) What are you,
microwaving?
Popcorn.
- Why don't you use
the microwave
in the kitchen, Phyllis?
- Someone needs to clean it.
It smells like popcorn.
Okay.
(microwave whirring)
I think of the Finer Things Club
as a little flickering candle
that everyone in the office is
trying to blow out
with their bad breath.
- [Jim] I can't believe
we're here.
I can't believe
this is happening.
- [Dwight] Believe it.
- Afro wig?
Do you want the afro wig?
- No, Michael, I'm not
leaving the car.
- You could be our getaway, man.
That's smart.
Keep the engine running.
- No, I am the "not
participating in any way" man.
- Come on!
- All right, Dwight.
Here's how it's
going to go down.
You and I...
(whispering)
Guy's going by. Shh,
You and I are going
to sneak inside.
We pretend that we are
warehouse workers.
And we will silly string the
bejesus out of the place.
- And if we have to defend
ourselves,
I will stab the security guard
in the eye with the jumbo chalk.
- No! No, you won't do that.
Nope.
- Then I'll grind up the jumbo
chalk and blow it in his eyes.
- Dwight, nothing
with the eyes, please.
Okay, Jim.
- Oh, my God. That's her.
That's her.
- Go go go go!
- Let's move! Move move move!
Shut up!
This is the dumbest
thing we've ever done.
- [Michael on radio] We are in
the stairwell.
- [Dwight] We are climbing
some stairs.
(heavy breathing)
- [Dwight] I am breathing
heavily.
- Okay, you know what?
You really don't need to be
updating me as much as
you're updating me.
- [Michael] There's a guy,
there's a guy.
- [Dwight] It's a security
guard coming by.
Hello. We're warehouse workers.
- Would you like more proof?
- [Guard] Hey.
- [Michael] Oh, my God.
That was very close.
- [Dwight] I can see the
security guard's eyes.
No, don't do anything to them!
- [Dwight] I have to do
something to his eyes.
The eyes are the groin
of the head.
- All right, Great Scott,
if you found that choking
hazard poster,
just head on home.
- [Michael] We got something
far better.
Their crown jewel.
They're industrial copier.
Isn't that thing huge?
- [Michael] It's enormous,
but it's got wheels.
We're wheeling it down
the hall into the stairwell.
Get the car ready.
Keep the engine running.
No, that is a terrible idea.
Don't do this.
- [Michael] Aahh!!!
(crashing sound)
[Dwight] My hip bone!
- [Michael] We're wedged between
the copier and the railing.
Ow! God! My leg!
- Leave us, Jim!
- Don't leave us!
- Save yourself!
- Don't leave us. Help us.
We need help, Jim.
- Okay, first of all,
stop using my name.
And second of all...
(Michael and Dwight arguing)
Damn it, guys.
Move over a little bit!
- I'm losing control
of my bladder!
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Karen is back.
- [Dwight] Is that Karen?
- [Michael] Take her to a motel.
Make love to her, Jim.
No, I'm not doing that.
- [Michael] Say you want to get
back together.
No, I'm not doing that.
- [Michael] It doesn't have
to mean anything.
Just do it for Stanley.
Come on, Jim.
Just climb on top of her
and think about Stanley.
Oh, Jim, if this is it for me,
promise me something...
- (taps on window)
- Jim?
[Michael] Host the Dundies.
Hey, Karen.
- Uhh... What are you
doing here?
First of all, Hi.
What are you doing here?
You good?
I'm just checking
on the other branches.
Michael wants me to do
that from time to time, so...
[Michael] Jim!
That's Michael right there.
Hold on a sec.
Utica's all set.
I'm going to head on to Albany.
- [Michael](moaning)
There's a crow bar
in the trunk.
Bring in the crow bar.
Why are you here?
I'm the getaway driver.
- [Dwight] Do not tell Karen
about the industrial copier
Copy that.
- I cried for weeks
over that guy.
So, yeah, seeing him
climb out of a PT Cruiser
in a lady's warehouse
uniform felt pretty good.
They sprayed me in the eye.
Scranton rules!
Stop it! Stop it!
(Dwight moans)
Can you help me, please?
I'm being crushed.
- And let me just add that as
a member of the Finer Things
Club, I would bring a strong
financial contribution to any
discretionary funds
that we may have.
Finally, here's a recommendation
from former
US Senator Rick Santorum.
Okay, that's enough.
Thanks, Andy.
He's going to ruin everything.
Oh, my God.
His letter of recommendation
from Rick Santorum
- is three fifty dollar bills.
- Wow.
Now we can afford
hardcover books.
I like it just us three.
I don't want it to change.
Let me ask you.
Did you accomplish
what you wanted?
- Listen, lady,
you can expect these kind
of repercussions as long as you
keep trying to poach our people.
I'm taking Stanley.
- And we will burn Utica
to the ground.
(Michael clears his throat)
- Granted, maybe this
was not the best idea.
But at least we care enough
about our employees that we
are willing to fight for them.
And if you so much as harm
a hair on Stanley's head,
we will burn Utica
to the ground.
- Jim, hang on a second.
- Yes.
- So you're still doing
this kind of stuff, huh?
- Yeah.
Trying to quit, though.
If you wanted to see me,
you could have just
called me like an adult.
- Oh, no, I didn't
want to see you.
Not that I'm not happy to be
seeing you right now.
I'm just saying, ultimately,
I was here for the copier.
Equal. I'd say it was equal.
So, good to see you.
(phones ringing)
I mean, it's just that...
(clears throat)
You know, Pam and
I are still dating, so...
And I just mean that things
are going really well.
So I didn't want to see you.
- Oh, things are going
really well, are they?
They are? That's great.
That's so great.
I want to hear more about
how happy you are with Pam.
Can you tell me more about that?
Thank you so much for coming
to Utica and breaking my copier
and telling me how well things
are going in your relationship.
Really. Thank you.
- All right.
You are welcome.
I am going to go
because of traffic.
- Traffic. Yeah.
- So...
- Go because of traff...
Definitely beat the traffic.
I will...
- I wasn't that mad at him,
but I needed time for Rolando
to put a scoop of tuna fish
in their glove compartment.
- Would it have killed you
to spend the afternoon making
love to her in a motel
room like I begged you to?
Pam would have understood.
Heck, Pam would have done it.
Pam is down for anything.
You embarrassed me.
You embarrassed us.
- Yeah, we should
have brought Andy.
I cut a chunk out
of my penis for nothing.
- Dear Andrew Bernard,
after carefully examining your
application to the
Finer Things Club.
We are unable to offer you a
position at this place in time.
We would, however,
like to place you on a list
in case an opportunity arises
when your inclusion
could be tolerated.
Your position as an ongoing
financial patron, however,
is yours to cherish.
Sincerely,
The Finer Things Club.
Yes!
Woohoo!
Wait listed.
I got into Cornell
off the wait list.
I went to Germany and did
a photojournalism project called
the Berlin Wall
Several Years Later.
Has anything really changed?
They ate it up.
Also, my dad went there.
He was a big donor.
I lived in Bernard Hall
my freshman year.
So...
- (clears throat)
- We tried and we failed.
Stanley, you
may go.
Here is a box
for your things.
But I doubt that that box
will be able to contain
all the memories that you
have of this place.
(Michael sighs)
Fly away, sweet little bird.
Fly away and be free.
Pam...
I'm going to need some
help writing a want ad.
Umm...
Wanted...
Middle aged black man with sass.
Big butt, bigger heart.
(knock on door)
I can't do this.
Michael?
A word?
Of course.
I changed my mind.
I want to keep this job.
- Really?
- Yes.
Because of the rapport we have
because of the family
that we have here?
- Yeah.
That's exactly the reason.
I wasn't really
planning on leaving.
All I wanted was a raise.
How on Earth did
Michael call my bluff?
Is he some sort
of secret genius?
(Stanley chuckles)
Sometimes I say crazy things.
Hey.
- I'm so sorry.
Rolando told me everything.
How humiliating.
Would it help you
to return to another age?
A time of refinement
and civility?
Are you inviting me
to the Finer Things Club?
(Andy gasps)
Oh, come on!
Frankie's prose is finer
than a pot of gold.
Say I.
Okay.
Did you get it out
of your system?
Yup.
No, I mean, I really liked it.
Thought it was a fun read.
Fun? Really?
- Yeah.
- What was fun about it for you?
Was it the death of the twins?
No, that wasn't fun.
Did you even read it?
Of course I read it.
[Oscar] How does it end?
Who's the main character?
Angela.
Nope.
Ashes.
(upbeat music)